there has been some media coverage this
week on the Ivy League universities
mainly Harvard it's still charging
$50,000 a year to go but the courses are
going to be online
the American government in summer now
decided that international students
aren't allowed to stay in America if
they're attending university classes
online but this video is about the Ivy
League education you were already
enrolled in it is until you are aware
that you were in this University it is
the most expensive tuition you will ever
pay it will cost you your life your
connection to self and others it will
cost you your health your finances
everything but once you're awake to it
you can if it cost you those things that
doesn't matter because you've enrolled
in University long before you were even
born the universe has a tailor-made
program for each and every one of us and
you can't help but be on it every time
there is a choice to do what society
says you're supposed to do or a
different choice for you to do what
calls from inside of you the option is
always to do the one that calls from
inside of you even if it's wrong even if
you made a mistake you will learn from
it and grow but it's your mistake to
make but if you choose society's path
and you wouldn't have necessarily if
they're the same path you're good you
listen to the things from inside of you
it happened to be in alignment no
problem but if you listen to society
when you were supposed to do something
else what it's here to teach you is to
not listen to society not listen to
society because if you get it right you
get the success you get the money there
isn't real happiness there because you
didn't listen to your own inner voice
you didn't do the thing that actually
would have taught you exactly what
you're here to learn I wouldn't help you
become your truest self you're becoming
a copy of something you're supposed to
be instead of who you truly are and that
is the biggest cost there is if you do
what society says you're supposed to do
and you get it wrong you are a failure
you have shame about that and you didn't
learn the lesson and so what society's
path is here to teach you is to be off
of it only on it when this one is the
same as this one once you start to learn
that you're here to follow your own
inner guide and the universe is here to
teach you exactly what you're supposed
to learn and the reflection of all the
human beings and events in front of you
and what your experience from that is
you start to learn that you can't
control anybody else's everyone else is
in their own University courses in their
own universe University University and
you start to have compassion for
something others you start to see how
everything in your past every challenge
every talent everything is inter woven
into you that is what you are here to do
who are you who are your people what is
your purpose I can give you your purpose
your purpose is to be you the u.s. you
there is anything you're not doing
because Society says you're not supposed
to but you would do otherwise anything
aside from the very very immortal is
yours to do and you will learn and the
universe will guide you as you follow
the course it's tailor-made you can't
get it wrong as long as you're trying to
listen to your inner voice because you
you don't even know what your inner
voice is until you listen to it and once
you start listening to it you're gonna
get it wrong you're gonna get it right
and every lesson is right every time you
listen to okay I'm just to go for this
walk I'm supposed to talk to this person
I'm supposed to you see that there was
something there and the universe
reconfigures itself no matter which path
you're on to reteach you teach you the
highest purpose it can with the choices
you've made but if you don't know you're
enrolled in it it is painful as hell and
once you are aware it's still painful in
the beginning and still a lot up to it
shouldnt to pay upfront because you are
going through a rollercoaster and losing
society's version of what you thought
you were supposed to be but what you
gain what's
you truly are enrolled in it you're just
like bring it out me what's the next
thing what's the next thing you got to
choose your own adventure University you
reverse enrolment and you're all in it
and it doesn't cost $50,000 a year it
costs everything when you learn to where
you're in it and it pays the highest
price it pays you the highest wage price
whatever you want to call it in
existence it gives you who you are and
then the government's the corporation's
can't take that away your friends and
family you can't take that away you
start to develop new friends and family
because you might lose them even many
lose them over discovering who you are
and on this side that looks like a price
too hard to pay and on the other side
there's it's like yes take more take
more I know there's more to give there's
more there's more there everything is a
lesson and everything is here to teach
us and you're already enrolled in the
university
you just got to wake up to it a better
worlds on its way and we all get to
participate in co-creating it together
please like and subscribe
it's the next time